Inventory of NYU Abu Dhabi Student Life Events: Photos, Music, and Videos Collection AD.RG.009.3-2-1
NYU Abu Dhabi, Archives and Special Collections
NYU Abu Dhabi Student Life Events: Photos, Music, and Videos
Fall 2013 - Spring 2020
NYU Abu Dhabi, Archives and Special Collections
AD.RG.009.3-2-1
78.97 Gigabytes for 4,900 items
Biographical / Historical
Programs of NYU Abu Dhabi Student Life, part of the Division of Student Affairs (previously Campus Life), include a variety of events and activities organized to cultivate engagement and inclusivity across the NYUAD campus. The Manager of Campus Facilities is part of a team of staff that advises on and arranges space and services to ensure events are successful. This includes photography and audiovisual arrangements. Historically, the Campus Facilities Managers have retained audiovisual content from events, especially in the institution's first decade.
Content Description
The NYU Abu Dhabi Student Life Events: Photos, Music, and Videos collection is a collection of digital images, as well as some music and video files, from a variety of student and campus events during Academic Years 2014 - 2020. The collection was maintained, organized and transferred to the University Archives by Student Affairs Facilities Manager, Declan Dowdall. Dowdall also transferred files he inherited from his predecessor, Alex Heald. Some administrative documents, such as brochures and event request forms, were included in the transfer and have been retained.
Events that are documented range from student field trips, to campus festivals, to other campus events such as Autism Awareness Week, Latino Night, Marhaba, Pakistani Mock Wedding, Staff Appreciation Day, and Defend the Nest, among others. Many of these events were, and some still are, understood as "campus traditions" during the institution's first decade.
See, for example, https://www.gonyuad.com/general/2017-18/releases/2018010837zguo
Arrangement
The collection has been minimally processed and its original arrangement by academic year has been retained. Within AY folders, the files are listed in alphabetical order.
Conditions Governing Access
This digital collection is accessible to members of the NYU Abu Dhabi community and the NYU Global Network.
- Student Life Event Coordinator, Fall 2013 - Spring 2015; 34.7 Megabytes
  Scope and Contents
  Mixed program and administrative files.
  - Student Life Brochure, June 20, 2013; 1 Sheets; 34.7 Megabytes (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-001)
    A draft copy of the 2013 Student Life brochure, with markups by Josh Taylor.
  - Budget, January-March, 2014; 2 Sheets; 34 Megabytes (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-002)
  - FileRelease, circa 2013; 2.4 Megabytes (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-003)
  - Flavors of Abu Dhabi, January - April, 2014; 2 Sheets; .0021 Megabytes (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-004)
  - Forms, 2014; 1 Sheets; .0017 Megabytes (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-005)
  - Linajma, 2013-2014; 6.4 Megabytes (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-006)
  - Ma_a Salama, 2015; 1 Sheets; .0014 Megabytes (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-007)
  - Marhaba, 2013; 1 Sheets; .0013 Megabytes (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-008)
  - Marhaba, 2014; .0417 Megabytes (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-009)
  - Newsletter, Fall 2013, Fall 2014, Spring 2015; .0214 Megabytes (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-010)
  - NYUAD Brand Pack, 2010-2011; 19.6 Megabytes (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-011)
  - Saadiyat, 2013; .0487 Megabytes (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-012)
  - Student Info, NYU NY, Fall 2013; .0053 Megabytes (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-013)
    Appraisal
    This document contains student PII (netID), may need to be redacted before providing access.
- AY13-14 (Alex Heald), Fall 2013 - Spring 2014; 429.7 Megabytes
  Images and documents maintained by the Manager of Student Life Facilities, Alex Heald, from the period 2013-2014.
  - Ajman Kashtah, 136 Megabytes (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-014)
  - AustraliaNZ, 51.2 Megabytes (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-015)
  - Autism Event (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-016)
  - Breakthrough (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-017)
  - Class of 2014 (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-018)
  - Dubai Kashtah (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-019)
  - Fujairah Camping (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-020)
  - GIN [Global Issues Network] 2014 (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-021)
  - HULT (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-022)
  - Latino Night (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-023)
  - Linajma (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-024)
  - Mangroves (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-025)
  - National Day (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-026)
  - Old Photos (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-027)
  - Random (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-028)
  - Sama Cup Outreach (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-029)
  - Saudi VIP (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-030)
  - Taste From Home Malaysian (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-031)
  - USA Canada Night (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-032)
- AY14-15 (Alex Heald), Fall 2014 - Spring 2015; 1.67 Gigabytes
  Includes images from a variety of events and field trips, maintained by Student Life Facilities Manager Alex Heald.
  - Al Wathba Camel Races, 2015; 1.39 Gigabytes for 175 items (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-033)
  - As One Screening, 2015; 10.9 Megabytes for 5 items (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-034)
  - Autism Awareness Lunch, 2015; 1 Megabytes for 2 images (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-035)
  - Class of 2015 Photos, 35 Megabytes for 5 items (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-036)
  - Community Outreach Fair, 2015; 4.6 Megabytes for 3 items (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-037)
  - Debate Championship, 2014; 1 Megabytes for 1 item (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-038)
  - Della Mae Bluegrass, 2015; 46.5 Megabytes for 4 items (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-039)
  - Diplomacy in Action, 2015; 156 Megabytes (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-040)
  - Dubomedy March 2015, 25.1 Megabytes (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-041)
  - East Asia Night, 2015; 1 Megabytes for one item (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-042)
  - Falcon's Flood, 2015; .1 Megabytes for 1 item (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-043)
  - Flavors - Russian Kitchen, 2015; 20.2 Megabytes for 2 items (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-044)
  - FYD Service Weekend, 2015; 8.4 Megabytes (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-045)
  - Terry Fox Run, 2015; 2.1 Megabytes for 1 item (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-046)
- AY14-15 (Declan Dowdall), Fall 2014 - Spring 2015; 483.6 Megabytes
  Images and audio files from academic year 2014-2015, maintained by Student Affairs Facilities Manager, Declan Dowdall.
  - Dubomedy March 2015, 184.4 Megabytes for 83 items (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-047)
  - Latino Night, 2015; 34.9 Megabytes for 10 items (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-048)
  - National Day 43 Event, 2014; 263.8 Megabytes for 74 items (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-049)
  - Saadiyat After Hours Event Calendar, February 2015; .492 Megabytes for one document (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-050)
- AY15-16 (Declan Dowdall), Fall 2015 - Spring 2016; 3.83 Gigabytes
  Images and some audiovisual files from academic year 2015-2016, maintained by Student Affairs Facilities Manager, Declan Dowdall.
  - Arab Culture Night, 2016; .820 Megabytes for 2 items (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-051)
  - Autism Awareness Walk [Abu Dhabi TV Footage], 2016; 192.4 Megabytes for one video (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-052)
  - Latino Night, 2016; 297.2 Megabytes for 45 items (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-053)
  - National Day 44 [music only], 2015; 266.5 Megabytes for 43 items (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-054)
  - Pakistani Mock Wedding [floor plan sketch - no images], 2016; .416 Megabytes for 1 item (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-055)
  - Park Hyatt Residence Images, 2016; 59.1 Megabytes for 17 items (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-056)
  - Spring Fest March 2016, 8.2 Megabytes for 5 items (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-057)
  - Tashan Sri Lankan New Year [event request form -- no images], 2016; .059 Megabytes for 2 documents (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-058)
- AY16-17 (Declan Dowdall), Fall 2016 - Spring 2017; 14.85 Gigabytes
  Images from academic year 2016-2017, maintained by Student Affairs Facilities Manager, Declan Dowdall.
  - Africa Carribean Night April 2017, 2.14 Gigabytes for 362 items (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-059)
  - Asia Pacific Night November 2016, 55.2 Megabytes for 17 items (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-060)
  - DJs in D1 March 2017, 609 Megabytes for 47 items (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-061)
  - Dubai Kashta and Etihad Museum Images 2017, 203 Megabytes for 18 items (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-062)
  - Dubomedy August 2017, 306 Megabytes for 36 items (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-063)
    Biographical / Historical
    https://www.dubomedy.com/
  - Halloween 2016, 177.5 Megabytes for 29 items (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-064)
  - Halloween Community NYUAD 2016, 1.61 Gigabytes for 287 items (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-065)
  - Latino Night 2017, 2.99 Gigabytes for 547 items (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-066)
  - Marhaba Captains and Leaders Karaoke Night, August 2016; 171 Megabytes for 29 items (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-068)
  - Marhaba Heritage Village, August 2016; 4.9 Megabytes for 2 items (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-069)
  - Marhaba Speed Meeting, August 2016; 14.4 Megabytes for 5 items (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-070)
  - Marhaba Variety Show, August 2016; 4.7 Megabytes for 1 item (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-071)
  - National Day 45, 2016; 1.16 Gigabytes for 247 items (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-072)
  - Pakistani Mock Wedding, 2017; 3.42 Gigabytes for 349 items (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-073)
  - Qhapag Nan [exhibition], 2017; 20.5 Megabytes for 8 items (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-074)
  - So You Think You Can't Dance February 2017, 22 Megabytes for 6 items (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-075)
  - Staff Appreciation Day October 2016, .257 Megabytes for 2 items (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-076)
  - Student Ball April 2017, 52.1 Megabytes (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-077)
  - Student Marhaba Dance Park Hyatt, August 2016; 122.2 Megabytes for 22 items (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-078)
  - Sufaraa BBQ February 2017, 18.2 Megabytes for 4 items (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-079)
  - Ultra Violet Live November 2016 [responses no images], 1 Megabytes for 1 document (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-080)
- AY17-18 (Declan Dowdall), Fall 2017 - Spring 2018; 27.14 Gigabytes
  Images and some audiovisual files from academic year 2017-2018, maintained by Student Affairs Facilities Manager, Declan Dowdall.
  - Attitide Just Dance September 2017, 1.36 Gigabytes for 18 items (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-081)
  - Awkward Dance Competition November 2017, 115.2 Megabytes for 6 items (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-082)
  - DJ Showcase October 2017, 15.8 Gigabytes for 34 items (images and video) (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-083)
  - Enrico Santacatterina Jam Session, April 2018; 29.1 Megabytes for 7 items (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-084)
  - First and Second Class Event Nov 2017 [no images], .0035 Megabytes (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-085)
  - Halloween Karaoke 2017 D1, 479.1 Megabytes for 58 items (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-086)
  - Halloween NYUAD 2017, 1.94 Gigabytes for 354 items (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-087)
  - Marhaba 2017 D1 Images, 455.5 Megabytes for 36 items (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-088)
  - Open Mic 2018, 133.3 Megabytes for 55 items (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-089)
  - Pakistani Mock Wedding April 2018, 1.48 Gigabytes for 81 items (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-090)
  - Pink Fitness Games October 2017, 29.5 Megabytes for 9 items (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-091)
  - Real AD Show September 2017, 3.44 Gigabytes for 56 items (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-092)
  - Staff Appreciation November 2017, 51 Megabytes for 8 items (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-093)
  - Volunteer Appreciation December 2017, 18.7 Megabytes for 5 items (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-094)
- AY18-19 (Declan Dowdall), Fall 2018 - Spring 2019; 7.2 Gigabytes
  Images and some audiovisual files from academic year 2018-2019, maintained by Student Affairs Facilities Manager, Declan Dowdall.
  - Arab Culture Club February 2019, 587.3 Megabytes for 64 items (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-095)
  - Holi March 2019, 21.1 Megabytes for 4 items (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-096)
  - Latino Night April 2019, 2.57 Gigabytes for 83 items (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-097)
  - Marhaba Student Govt Dance August 2018, 1.89 Gigabytes for 69 items (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-098)
  - Staff Appreciation Day April 2019, 2.13 Gigabytes for 158 items (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-099)
- AY19-20 (Declan Dowdall), Fall 2019 - Spring 2020; 28.5 Gigabytes
  Images and some audiovisual files from academic year 2019-2020, maintained by Student Affairs Facilities Manager, Declan Dowdall.
  - ADNH Top Chef September 2019, 2.28 Gigabytes for 56 items (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-100)
  - Afro Fest November 2019, 2.24 Gigabytes for 82 items (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-101)
  - BK Gulf Event 21 January 2020, 95.2 Megabytes for 1 item (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-102)
  - Defeat the Deans November 2019, 586.4 Megabytes for 21 items (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-103)
  - Defend the Nest November 2019, 1.34 Gigabytes for 54 items (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-104)
  - Diwali November 2019, 1.35 Gigabytes for 35 items (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-105)
  - Falcon Feast September 2019, 3.44 Gigabytes for 96 items (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-106)
  - Go Green Group Photos February 2020, 130.9 Megabytes for 5 items (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-107)
  - GO Green Week February 2020, 1.3 Gigabytes for 57 items (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-108)
  - Hazel and Jay December 2019, 3.43 Gigabytes for 127 items (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-109)
  - Jackie Soul Food February 2020, 142.6 Megabytes for 5 items (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-110)
  - John Sexton Talk October 2019, 149.5 Megabytes for 23 items (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-111)
  - Marhaba Carnival 2019, 2.95 Gigabytes for 61 items (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-112)
  - Marhaba Welcome Dance August 2019, 2.19 Gigabytes for 44 items (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-113)
  - MSF [Medecins Sans Frontieres] November 2019, 331.6 Megabytes for 51 items (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-114)
  - National Day 48 December 2019, 448.4 Megabytes for 28 items (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-115)
  - Nurdle Hunt November 2019, 2.53 Gigabytes for 116 items (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-116)
  - Hamilton December 2019, 308 Megabytes for 35 items (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_117)
  - Staff Appreciation Day October 2019, 361.7 Megabytes for 53 items (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-118)
  - Student Life Open House 16 September 2019, 2.12 Gigabytes for 81 items (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-119)
  - Swimming Pool January 2020, 121 Megabytes for 1 item (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-120)
  - UAE Majlis SIG September 2019, 648.2 Megabytes for 24 items (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-121)